{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_Hospital",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Bruce_Davison",
    "human_readable": "Bruce Davison stars in Kingdom Hospital.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7399665117263794,
            "question": "What movie stars Bruce Davison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6266769170761108,
            "question": "What is the title of the television series starring Bruce Davison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5896046161651611,
            "question": "In which television series does Bruce Davison appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5685415267944336,
            "question": "Who is the lead actor in Kingdom Hospital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45029014348983765,
            "question": "Is Bruce Davison known for any particular role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.361507385969162,
            "question": "Name a film or TV show featuring Bruce Davison."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3126164972782135,
            "question": "What is Bruce Davison's most famous role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21690446138381958,
            "question": "What genre is Kingdom Hospital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20220337808132172,
            "question": "Does Bruce Davison have any other notable acting credits?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1898297369480133,
            "question": "Has Bruce Davison appeared in other horror-related projects?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bruce Davison stars in Kingdom Hospital.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7233_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Bruce Davison have any other notable acting credits?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7233_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Kingdom Hospital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7233_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bruce Davison's most famous role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7233_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7233_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer to your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nAccording to the documents, Bruce Davison plays the role of Dr. Stegman on Stephen King's Kingdom Hospital (2004-2005), and also stars in a film or TV movie called \"Kingdom\", which is likely referring to the same series. Therefore, the information supports that Bruce Davison stars in Kingdom Hospital."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Bruce Allen Davison starred in the TV series \"Kingdom Hospital (2004-2005)\" and also mentions his role as Dr. Stegman on the TV movie/series \"Stephen King's Kingdom Hospital,\" which supports the statement that Bruce Davison stars in Kingdom Hospital."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}